I recently learned something about the Congo that absolutely blew my mind.
And I know it's going to blow yours too, because this is not widely known information.
And you know, hopefully my page doesn't get taken down for this.
Because remember, guys, we must protect the war machine.
We must protect the war machine at all costs.
The war machine is our friend.
So this is what I learned.
The bombs that were dropped on Hiroshima and Nagasaki were made from minerals that come from the Congo.
I'm going to let that sink in and say it again.
The bombs that America dropped on Japan in World War II were only made possible because of Congolese mines.
I don't even know where to begin.
Oh my goodness.
I feel like bursting into tears right now from the sheer overwhelm of how much work needs to be done and how far behind we are.
Because when we talk about the Congo, we're always talking about, you know, cell phones and electric cars and batteries and shit.
When in reality, the Congo is also essential to the war machine.
In fact, there is no war machine as we know it today without the Congo, without African minerals in general.
And this is why they had to assassinate Lumumba, because he was not going to give them access anymore to those mines.
Congo has been exploited for decades.
I am so sorry.
I don't even know where to begin with this.
Like, I don't even know what to do with this information because of how grave it is.
There is no war machine without Congo, without Africa.
Like, I need this to sink in.
And how do I know about this?
Because I watched this documentary called Soundtrack to the Coup d'Etat.
Or Soundtrack to a Coup d'Etat.
Which is a documentary about how the CIA arranged this concert in the Congo.
They sent Black American artists like Louis Armstrong and Nina Simone and other jazz artists to Congo to distract people from the CIA-backed coup d'etat that was happening.
To deflect from what they were doing.
I'm going to just end the video here.